{
    "subject": "resource/G._E._M._Anscombe",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1919_births",
    "human_readable": "The subject of G.E.M. Anscombe is 1919 births.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.775682270526886,
            "question": "In what year was G.E.M. Anscombe born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7716802954673767,
            "question": "What significance does the year 1919 hold in relation to G.E.M. Anscombe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7339845895767212,
            "question": "What is known about G.E.M. Anscombe's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6348513960838318,
            "question": "Were there any notable philosophical developments during the year of G.E.M. Anscombe's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6158159375190735,
            "question": "What historical events might have been happening during G.E.M. Anscombe's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5667238831520081,
            "question": "Can you tell me anything about G.E.M. Anscombe based on her birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5357754826545715,
            "question": "What can we infer about G.E.M. Anscombe's early life based on her birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.523560106754303,
            "question": "Was G.E.M. Anscombe born in the 20th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4908404052257538,
            "question": "How might her birth year have influenced G.E.M. Anscombe's life and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20229198038578033,
            "question": "Is there a connection between the year 1919 and any major philosophical schools of thought?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of G.E.M. Anscombe is 1919 births.",
            "html": "dbpedia_676_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might her birth year have influenced G.E.M. Anscombe's life and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_676_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was G.E.M. Anscombe born in the 20th century?",
            "html": "dbpedia_676_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we infer about G.E.M. Anscombe's early life based on her birth year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_676_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_676_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that G. E. M. Anscombe was born on March 18, 1919. Therefore, supporting the triple that the subject of G.E.M. Anscombe is related to 1919 births."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}